Guide to the Football Game Film Collection, 1934-2007 UA.13.01.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Game Films
  - Navy, 1946 October 12
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 October 12; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0113)
  - Richmond, 1946 October 19
    Duke win, score: 41-0
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 October 19; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0114)
  - Army, 1946 October 26
    Duke loss, score: 0-19
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 October 26; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0115)
  - Georgia Tech, 1946 November 02
    Duke loss, score: 0-14
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0116)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0117)
  - Wake Forest, 1946 November 09
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 09; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 59, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0118)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 09; BetaCamSP
  - South Carolina, 1946 November 16
    Duke win, score: 39-0
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 16; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0119)
  - North Carolina, 1946 November 23
    Duke loss, score: 7-22
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1946 November 23; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0120)
  - Sports Parade, Fall 1947
    - Sports Parade, Fall 1947; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 50, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0121)
  - NC State, 1947 September 27
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 September 27; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0122)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 September 27; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0123)
  - Tennessee, 1947 October 04
    Duke win, score: 19-7
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 October 04; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0124)
  - Navy, 1947 October 11
    Duke T, score: 14-14
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 October 11; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0125)
  - Maryland, 1947 October 18
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 October 18; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0126)
  - Wake Forest, 1947 October 25
    Duke win, score: 13-6
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 October 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0127)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 October 25; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0128)
  - Missouri, 1947 November 08
    Duke loss, score: 7-28
    - Duke vs. Missouri: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 November 08; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0129)
  - South Carolina, 1947 November 15
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 November 15; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 60, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0130)
  - North Carolina, 1947 November 22
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 November 22; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 135, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0131)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1947 November 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0132)
  - Unknown opponent, circa 1948-1949
    - Duke vs. Unknown opponent: Unidentified game coverage, circa 1948-1949; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0133)
  - NC State, 1948 September 25
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 September 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0134)
  - Tennessee, 1948 October 02
    Duke T, score: 7-7
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 October 02; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0135)
  - Navy, 1948 October 09
    Duke win, score: 28-7
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 October 09; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0136)
  - Maryland, 1948 October 16
    Duke win, score: 13-12
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 October 16; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0137)
  - Virginia Tech, 1948 October 23
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 October 23; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 110, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0138)
  - Georgia Tech, 1948 October 30
    Duke loss, score: 7-19
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 October 30; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0139)
  - George Washington, 1948 November 13
    Duke win, score: 62-0
    - Duke vs. George Washington: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 November 13; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0140)
  - North Carolina, 1948 November 20
    Duke loss, score: 0-20
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1948 November 20; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0141)
  - Richmond, 1949 September 24
    Duke win, score: 67-0
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1949 September 24; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0142)
  - Navy, 1949 October 08
    Duke loss, score: 14-28
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1949 October 08; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 61, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0143)
  - Virginia Tech, 1949 October 22
    Duke win, score: 56-7
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1949 October 22; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0144)
  - Georgia Tech, 1949 October 29
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1949 October 29; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0145)
  - Highlights, circa 1950s
    - Highlights, circa 1950s; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 115, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0146)
  - South Carolina, 1950 September 23
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 September 23; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0147)
  - Pittsburgh, 1950 September 30
    Duke win, score: 28-14
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 September 30; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 104, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0148)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 September 30; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0149)
  - Tennessee, 1950 October 07
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 October 07; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0150)
  - NC State, 1950 October 14
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 October 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0151)
  - Richmond, 1950 October 21
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 October 21; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 64, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0152)
    - Duke vs. Richmond: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 October 21; DVD
  - Maryland, 1950 October 28
    Duke loss, score: 14-26
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 October 28; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0153)
  - Georgia Tech, 1950 November 04
    Duke win, score: 30-21
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 November 04; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0154)
  - Wake Forest, 1950 November 11
    Duke loss, score: 7-13
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 November 11; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 133, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0155)
  - Virginia Tech, 1950 November 18
    Duke win, score: 47-6
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 November 18; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 134, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0156)
  - North Carolina, 1950 November 25
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1950 November 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0157)
  - Oldtimers, 1951 April 14
    Duke win, score: 21-7
    - Duke vs. Oldtimers: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 April 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0158)
  - Football Parade, Fall 1951
    - Football Parade, Fall 1951; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 52, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0159)
  - End Zone Shots, Fall 1951
    - End Zone Shots, Fall 1951; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0160)
  - South Carolina, 1951 September 22
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 September 22; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0161)
  - Pittsburgh, 1951 September 29
    Duke win, score: 19-14
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 September 29; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0162)
  - Tennessee, 1951 October 06
    Duke loss, score: 0-26
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 October 06; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0163)
  - NC State, 1951 October 13
    Duke win, score: 27-21
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 October 13; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0164)
  - Virginia Tech, 1951 October 20
    Duke win, score: 56-6
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 October 20; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0165)
  - Virginia, 1951 October 27
    Duke loss, score: 7-30
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 October 27; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0166)
  - Georgia Tech, 1951 November 03
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 November 03; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0167)
  - Wake Forest, 1951 November 10
    Duke loss, score: 13-19
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 November 10; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 132, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0168)
  - William & Mary, 1951 November 17
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 November 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 104, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0169)
  - North Carolina, 1951 November 24
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1951 November 24; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0170)
  - End Zone Shots, Fall 1952
    - End Zone Shots, Fall 1952; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 116, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0171)
  - Washington and Lee, 1952 September 20
    - Duke vs. Washington and Lee: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 September 20; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0172)
  - Southern Methodist, 1952 September 26
    - Duke vs. Southern Methodist: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 September 26; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0173)
  - Tennessee, 1952 October 04
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 October 04; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0174)
  - South Carolina, 1952 October 11
    Duke win, score: 33-7
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 October 11; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0175)
  - NC State, 1952 October 18
    Duke win, score: 57-0
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 October 18; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0176)
  - Virginia, 1952 October 25
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 October 25; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 131, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0177)
  - Georgia Tech, 1952 November 01
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 November 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0178)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 November 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0179)
  - Navy, 1952 November 08
    Duke loss, score: 6-16
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 November 08; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0180)
  - Wake Forest, 1952 November 15
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 November 15; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0181)
  - North Carolina, 1952 November 22
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1952 November 22; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 127, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0182)
  - South Carolina, 1953 September 19
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 1 of 2, 1953 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0183)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: 2 of 2, 1953 September 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0184)
  - Wake Forest, 1953 September 26
    Duke win, score: 19-0
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 September 26; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0185)
  - Tennessee, 1953 October 03
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 03; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0186)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 03; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0187)
  - Purdue, 1953 October 10
    Duke win, score: 20-14
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 10; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 113, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0188)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 10; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0189)
  - Army, 1953 October 17
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 17; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0190)
    - Duke vs. Army: Highlights, 1953 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0191)
      Has sound
    - Duke vs. Army: TV Highlights, 1953 October 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0192)
  - NC State, 1953 October 24
    Duke win, score: 31-0
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 24; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0193)
  - Virginia, 1953 October 31
    Duke win, score: 48-6
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 October 31; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0194)
  - Navy, 1953 November 07
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 November 07; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0195)
  - Georgia Tech, 1953 November 21
    Duke loss, score: 10-13
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: regular, 1953 November 21; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0196)
  - North Carolina, 1953 November 28
    Duke win, score: 35-20
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1953 November 28; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0197)
  - Highlights, Fall 1954
    Highlight reel; Home Security Life Game Film
    - Highlights, Fall 1954; 16mm film (11" reel) (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0198)
    - Highlights, Fall 1954; 16mm film (11" reel) (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0199)
  - End Zone Shots, Fall 1954
    "USC, Tech, Tenn."
    - End Zone Shots, Fall 1954; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 126, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0200)
  - Pennsylvania, 1954 September 25
    Duke win, score: 52-0
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 September 25; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0201)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 September 25; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 124, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0202)
    - Duke vs. Pennsylvania: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 September 25; DVD
  - Tennessee, 1954 October 02
    Duke win, score: 7-6
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 02; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0203)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 02; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 124, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0204)
  - Purdue, 1954 October 09
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Defense 1, 1954 October 09; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0205)
    - Duke vs. Purdue: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 09; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 106, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0206)
      Home Security Life Game Film
  - Army, 1954 October 16
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 16; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0207)
    - Duke vs. Army: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 16; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0208)
  - NC State, 1954 October 23
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 23; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0209)
  - Georgia Tech, 1954 October 30
    Duke win, score: 21-20
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 October 30; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0210)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 1 of 3, 1954 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0211)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 2 of 3, 1954 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0212)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: 3 of 3, 1954 October 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0213)
  - Navy, 1954 November 06
    Duke loss, score: 7-40
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 06; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 122, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0214)
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 06; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 122, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0215)
  - Wake Forest, 1954 November 13
    Duke win, score: 28-21
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 13; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 106, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0216)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 13; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 129, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0217)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 13; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0218)
  - South Carolina, 1954 November 20
    Duke win, score: 26-7
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 20; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0219)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 20; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0220)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 20; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 130, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0221)
  - North Carolina, 1954 November 27
    Duke win, score: 47-12
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 27; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 112, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0222)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1954 November 27; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0223)
  - Orange Bowl Parade, 1955 January 01
    - Orange Bowl Parade, 1955 January 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0224)
  - Nebraska, 1955 January 01
    Orange Bowl. Duke win, score: 34-7
    - Duke vs. Nebraska: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 January 01; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 67, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0225)
    - Duke vs. Nebraska: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 January 01; DVD
    - Duke vs. Nebraska: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 January 01; DigiBeta
  - Football Parade, Fall 1955
    - Football Parade, Fall 1955; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 94, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0226)
  - Navy, 1955 September 01
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 September 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0227)
  - NC State, 1955 September 24
    - Duke vs. NC State: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 September 24; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0228)
    - Duke vs. NC State: regular, 1955 September 24; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0229)
  - Tennessee, 1955 October 01
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 01; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 109, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0230)
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: 1 of 3, 1955 October 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 101, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0231)
  - William & Mary, 1955 October 08
    Duke win, score: 47-7
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 08; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0232)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 08; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 114, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0233)
  - Ohio State, 1955 October 15
    - Duke vs. Ohio State: 2 of 2, 1955 October 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0234)
      Duplication
  - Pittsburgh, 1955 October 22
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 22; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 63, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0235)
  - Georgia Tech, 1955 October 29
    Duke loss, score: 0-27
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 29; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 62, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0236)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 29; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 126, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0237)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 October 29; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 126, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0238)
  - Navy, 1955 November 05
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 05; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0239)
      Script accompanying 12" reel
    - Duke vs. Navy: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 05; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box missing, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0240)
  - South Carolina, 1955 November 12
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 107, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0241)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 65, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0242)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0243)
      Dub by unknown source
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0244)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 58, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0245)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 12; VHS
  - Wake Forest, 1955 November 19
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 19; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 108, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0246)
      Script accompanies 12" reel
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 November 19; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 126, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0247)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1 of 2, 1955 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0248)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2 of 2, 1955 November 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 103, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0249)
  - North Carolina, 1955 December 03
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 December 03; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0250)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1955 December 03; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 128, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0251)
  - Football Parade, Fall 1956
    - Football Parade, Fall 1956; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 105, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0252)
  - South Carolina, 1956 September 22
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Unidentified game coverage, 1956 September 22; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 125, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0253)
  - Virginia, 1956 September 29
    Duke win, score: 40-7
    - Duke vs. Virginia: regular, 1956 September 29; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 123, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0254)
  - Tennessee, 1956 October 06
    Duke loss, score: 20-33
    - Duke vs. Tennessee: regular, 1956 October 06; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 125, Film-reel UA13010004-F16-0255)